recruiterbox.com 2019-11-02

# Privacy Policy | Recruiterbox

Last updated: March 18, 2019

This Applied Training Systems, Inc.*, a Delaware corporation (“ATSI”) Privacy Policy regulates the collection, use and disclosure of information collected on the website and application located at recruiterbox.com. By using this website and/or application, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. You always have the choice not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us and to take advantage of certain functionality. If you do not agree to these terms, you are prohibited from using this website and/or application and should exit immediately. You acknowledge that the Privacy Policy is subject to modification and that your continued use of the site constitutes agreement with the then-current terms of the Privacy Policy. The date of the most recent update can be found at the top of the document.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection and Use

ATSI collects information to better serve our customers and visitors to recruiterbox.com. When we have a better picture of how people are using our website and application, we can improve the experience of our users.

The information we gather depends on the area involved and the portion of the website/application being visited. For password protected areas, we capture information including the username and the date, time, and/or length of the visit. In other areas, we record information that you affirmatively provide to us.

For many areas of our application, accounts are provisioned under an agreement that ATSI has established with the entity providing your employment or training services (such agreement, “Customer Agreement”). Some of this information may be provided and accessed by the entity which your account is provisioned. Your use of the application is conditioned on the Customer Agreement, and you may lose access to the application at any time should the Customer Agreement terminate. Further, you understand that the entity may access any information that we collect from or about you through the application.

If you want to be able to receive information from ATSI, you may provide your name and contact information to us through the website. By doing so, you consent to receive communications from ATSI.

We will not sell or rent your information to other marketers. Your personal information will only be disclosed to a third party (other than as described herein) upon a merger or reorganization between us and such a third party or as needed to provide technical support or development for the website or application, or as required to process subscription payment transactions.

### Cookies and Log Data

For general visitors to our websites, we use “cookies” and other tools to collect information about users’ visits, such as which pages of the site are visited and for how long. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Cookies are required to use all ATSI services. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you will not be able to use portions of our service and website.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our service’s functionality. We take responsibility in validating controls and compliance of any and all third party subprocessors of this information.

### Disclosure and Legal Compliance

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our service.

### Links to Other Sites

Our websites will occasionally have links to other websites that are not operated by ATSI. We are not responsible for the contents of those websites and have no control over what information they may or may not collect from you.

### Data Storage

ATSI uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run ATSI services. Although ATSI owns the code, databases, and all rights to the ATSI suite of applications, you retain all rights to your data.

### Data Transfer

We may transfer your personal information to our service providers and others located in the United States or elsewhere in the world for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements, and some, including the United States, provide less legal protection for your personal information than others. Please know, however, that no matter where your personal information is collected, used, transferred or stored, if it was collected through our websites, it will be governed by and used in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from visitors under the age of 13. If you are a parent and you discover that your child under the age of 13 provided personal information to us, please let us know and we will delete that information from our files.

### EU Privacy Shield

ATSI complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States.  ATSI has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, ATSI commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact ATSI at:

ATSI has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regards to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship. If timely acknowledgment of your complaint is not received from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint.  The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

ATSI commits to cooperate with EU DPA’s and comply with the advice given by EU DPA’s with regards to human resources data transferred from ATSI in the context of the employment relationship.

ATSI does not disclose personal information to third parties, unless required to do so in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, ATSI is potentially liable. Individuals have the right to access their personal data as long as a.) the individual is in good standing with their organization b.) the organization is a customer in good standing with ATSI. Individual personal data is accessible by the identified, customer-appointed system administrator of the ATSI system (contact support to identify your system administrator.) ATSI is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and/or the Department of Transportation. Individuals have the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration before a Privacy Shield Panel.

### Personal Information

Through your account, you may access, and, in some cases, edit personal information collected by the application. We will make reasonable efforts to provide you with access or correct such information if it is inaccurate or delete such information if we are not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. Please note that our Customer Agreement may require that we preserve certain information in your account unchanged. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to contact us to prevent disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes; in order to submit such a request, please contact us at support@recruiterbox.com.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

### Questions

If you wish to view, update, or delete personally identifiable information that ATSI has stored about you, or you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us at:

ATSI

911 E. Pike Street, Suite #333

Seattle, WA 98122

support@recruiterbox.com

_*ATSI includes the entities of Reviewsnap, Promantek (dba Trakstar), Recruiterbox, and Mindflash._
